<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elhoucine Azayou offcial website</title>
    <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Elhoucine Azayou offcial website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:13:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://elhoucine.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The art of building a product</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/the-art-of-building-a-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/the-art-of-building-a-product/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-best-product:9c5860720c439fc0d89a5fca1a01d17e&#34;&gt;What is the best product?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best product is the one people want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The great marketing tells people why they need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Build something people want, and tell them about it. That&amp;rsquo;s the art of building a product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-your-product-sells-your-marketing-or-your-marketing-sells-you-product:9c5860720c439fc0d89a5fca1a01d17e&#34;&gt;Does your product sells your marketing, or your marketing sells you product?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;A lot of founders really struggle trying to market and sell something that people don’t want or don’t need. If your product is crap, there is no marketing strategy — and no source of investment — that can keep it alive for long.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoted from this impressive story &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.freecodecamp.com/growing-a-side-project-into-a-17-000-month-business-46024d2aa87f#.qz22hz7p2&#34;&gt;How my friends and I grew our side project into a $17,000/month&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-apple-uses-marketing:9c5860720c439fc0d89a5fca1a01d17e&#34;&gt;How Apple uses marketing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is iPhone 7, it makes all the things you do with your iPhone better, faster, and more powerful.&lt;/em&gt; These were the first words in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q6dsRpVyyWs&#34;&gt;this iPhone 7 ad&lt;/a&gt; from apple. They tell you exactly why you need to buy this new iPhone. That&amp;rsquo;s the marketing, and if it&amp;rsquo;s NOT packed with something you want, then it&amp;rsquo;s just crap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion:9c5860720c439fc0d89a5fca1a01d17e&#34;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Building something people want seems easy. In theory, it is, but it is not in practice. Building something people want often means listening to them, caring about them, getting their feedback seriously. And top of all knowing your users and sticking with them, one can not satisfy the whole population.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A great idea</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/a-great-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/a-great-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I never had the chance -yet- to find a great idea, I decided maybe writing about it could be a good start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before, it looked unpromising, but after execution people loves it, it becomes an everyday life thing! That was my definition of the great idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If at first, the idea is not absurd, then there is no hope for it.” ― Albert Einstein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See how existing successful ideas were perceived at the beginning, they were almost weird, crazy, or impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great ideas are outside the fashion, they are uncomfortable to work with, they demand more effort, vision, different thinking and sometimes dreaming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing things from different perspectives helps. I am fan of healthy fast food business, my imagination is always on: what if I can open an app customize my healthy sandwich (The work done by trained robots) and receive it by drone, it should be healthier, faster and cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing perspectives could be a good exercise for to look for new, fresh, and potential great ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, not all great ideas will work, and they will remain simple ideas until executed, in fact, only the execution shows how great your idea is. If it is great enough you may be lucky succeeding with a poor looking but a functional product. Sometimes even if you start fancy, success may not be your friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Timing, environment, and people are part of the execution and success equation. If you got some or them all, then bingo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tranquility</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/tranquility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 15:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/tranquility/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;less-but-better:9a65cd3722e81b2858f6df65f0a543d1&#34;&gt;Less but better.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you seek tranquillity, do less.” Or (more accurately) do what’s essential—what the logos of a social being requires, and in the requisite way. Which brings a double satisfaction: to do less, better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because most of what we say and do is not essential. If you can eliminate it, you’ll have more time, and more tranquillity. Ask yourself at every moment, “Is this necessary?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we need to eliminate unnecessary assumptions as well. To eliminate the unnecessary actions that follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;satisfaction:9a65cd3722e81b2858f6df65f0a543d1&#34;&gt;Satisfaction.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then you might see what the life of the good man is like—someone content with what nature assigns him, and satisfied with being just and kind himself. »&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accept:9a65cd3722e81b2858f6df65f0a543d1&#34;&gt;Accept.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;« You’ve seen that. Now look at this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t be disturbed. Uncomplicate yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone has done wrong … to himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something happens to you. Good. It was meant for you by nature, woven into the pattern from the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is short. That’s all there is to say. Get what you can from the present—thoughtfully, justly.
Unrestrained moderation. »&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quoted from Meditations, by Aurelius, Marcus. Book 4 (24, 25, &amp;amp; 26).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am ashamed of</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/i-am-ashamed-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 09:43:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/i-am-ashamed-of/</guid>
      <description>&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;“If most of us are ashamed of shabby clothes and shoddy furniture, let us be more ashamed of shabby ideas and shoddy philosophies.”
Albert Einstein
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We become obsessed with appearances, that we may judge people by what they wear, worst, treat them depending on it, even worst, doing it with our selves as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet we don&amp;rsquo;t question the quality of the ideas we are feeding to our selves, as that this matter doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://bashooka.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/conceptual-photography-bshk-10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;look inside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As shabby clothes, shabby ideas exist too, &lt;code&gt;I can&#39;t do it&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;I should wear a suit to look serious&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;It is too late to do it&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;I am a failure&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;racism&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Préjugés&lt;/code&gt;&amp;hellip; Why aren&amp;rsquo;t we ashamed of these as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this comes from 3 things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Obey society’s expectations&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Conformity&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Lack of mono confidence&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With &lt;code&gt;mono confidence&lt;/code&gt; I mean to be confident in doing what others don&amp;rsquo;t expect you to do, to upset them with your doings, meaning instead of being embarrassed by doing what they are not expecting you to do, you upset them by doing it, while being totally comfortable. In other words, to believe in and follow your dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of the successful people through history were &lt;code&gt;minimalists&lt;/code&gt; they preferred living a simple life, they refused to be trapped by
society&amp;rsquo;s expectations, they saw the word differently, they do the things that no one does, and that was the key to their greatness.
Einstein was one of them, and yet after sixty years of his death, his name is continuingly appearing everywhere, thanks to his quotes, books, ideas, philosophies&amp;hellip; Not to his clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am ashamed of shabby ideas and shoddy philosophies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Look at the inside&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books: The Icarus Deception: How High Will You Fly?</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/books-the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:34:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/books-the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The book I read last month (august 2016) was The Icarus Deception: How High Will You Fly?
Book by Seth Godin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://t1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTNW3STRX26TWTpainrWHiplcngpFc1Uqxoqty6pFKXA9QJMi0x&#34; alt=&#34;The Icarus Deception: How High Will You Fly?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, this book calls your inner creative person, and it is trying to wake up the sleeping artist inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are brainwashed by industrialism to playing it safe, not taking risks, and not flying too high, follow your boss instructions and shut down you inner voice. The book is about the other way, the ART way, it will challenge you in ways that may surprise you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As someone who loves ART, this book challenges me and made me think through it&amp;rsquo;s chapters, about the fear from making ART and facing the world, the fear from critics and rejection. Each time I opened the book I felt like it&amp;rsquo;s the right time to read that set of pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If one take away: Make better ART (work).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Everyone knows that Icarus’s father made him wings and told him not to fly too close to the sun; he ignored the warning and plunged to his doom. The lesson: Play it safe. Listen to the experts. It was the perfect propaganda for the industrial economy. What boss wouldn’t want employees to believe that obedience and conformity are the keys to success?

But we tend to forget that Icarus was also warned not to fly too low, because seawater would ruin the lift in his wings. Flying too low is even more dangerous than flying too high, because it feels deceptively safe.

The safety zone has moved. Conformity no longer leads to comfort. But the good news is that creativity is scarce and more valuable than ever. So is choosing to do something unpredictable and brave: Make art. Being an artist isn’t a genetic disposition or a specific talent. It’s an attitude we can all adopt. It’s a hunger to seize new ground, make connections, and work without a map. If you do those things you’re an artist, no matter what it says on your business card.

Godin shows us how it’s possible and convinces us why it’s essential.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unfinished race against time</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/the-unfinished-race-against-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 11:49:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/the-unfinished-race-against-time/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We often get busy doing what we do in our lives without taking the time to think clearly about the meaning and the impact of what we are doing. I think one should at least figure out what really matters to him and figure out how to live according to that. I know that life is hard but living a unfinished race against time is even harder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-it-have-meaning-for-me:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Does it have meaning &lt;strong&gt;for me&lt;/strong&gt; ?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a good question to answer, because what we do determines who we are, and who we will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Is what I am doing worth telling to my children ?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A normal, and a calculated-for-safety life is boring to tell, only the &lt;strong&gt;risky&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;challenging&lt;/strong&gt;, unusual life is worth telling, and interesting, and capturing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;risky&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;challenging&lt;/strong&gt;, and unusual life is like a movie, where you are the protagonist, you have a goal in mind, there is plenty of obstacles, you may suffer, you may give up for some time, but you fight again until you achieve what&amp;rsquo;s yours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;caring-about-the-world:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Caring about the world.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caring about the world is something meaningful, because &lt;strong&gt;we are not living alone&lt;/strong&gt;, and our lives depends on each other, and you are not only a citizen of your country, you are a citizen of the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world needs us more than ever, it needs us to follow our dreams, to live purely, to be human, to connect and to care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;doing-art:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Doing ART!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;I want them to discover that they are artists;
everyone is an artist, a creator, and refiner of sensibility without knowing it.
--Yves Klein
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art is a form of freedom, because to do art is to listen to our inner voice, and imagination, it is about doing one&amp;rsquo;s original version. So rather that following instructions we create them. Doing an original/quality work, or making someone&amp;rsquo;s day is also an form of ART.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-with-others:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Connecting with others.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;We are like islands in the sea, separate on the surface but connected in the deep.
― William James
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this may be the most meaningful thing on earth, connecting with other people, discovering new cultures&amp;hellip; Travel is a way of doing that, and that&amp;rsquo;s what I like most about traveling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-with-self:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Connecting with self.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;The most beautiful things can only be created by the most free minds!
― Mehmet Murat ildan
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world where the sky is upon our heads, where space is filled with few vital but many trivial things, we will barely breath, and we will barely live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freeing our mind, eliminating the external noise, and making space for what matters, is the core to keep our mind in good state and our life under control.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am committed in joining Toptal ?</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/why-i-am-committed-in-joining-toptal-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 16:50:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/why-i-am-committed-in-joining-toptal-/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you search on Google you will find similar posts with the same title as this post. Because writing a blogpost about it helps you speed up the process and get &amp;lsquo;Priority Access&amp;rsquo; to the Toptal platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, was that my motivation to write it ? Definitely Not!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the completing your profile section, I got asked if I want a &amp;lsquo;Priority Access&amp;rsquo; then I have to write a blog post on my website explaining
why I am committed in joining Toptal, I skipped it right away, because it simply didn&amp;rsquo;t motivate me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After skipping it, I asked my self, seriously, why I am admitted in joining the Toptal Web Developers Network anyway ?  And hell, yeah! the desire to answer this question, and write a blog post about it comes suddenly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is the answer to that why, summed in 3 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1- &lt;strong&gt;Freelancing&lt;/strong&gt;:
The obvious motivation is of course freelancing, after doing full-time job for a while, it didn&amp;rsquo;t work well for me, so I decided to work remotely, because simply I found it hard to stick in one place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2- &lt;strong&gt;Quality&lt;/strong&gt;:
Okay, looking at all the open-source platforms, where everybody try to sell them selves, and the need to deal with automatic examination and test which by the way easy to crack, it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the best option for me, so I had to look for better. Toptal selection is human made, and the process is serious. And that explains well the 3% promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3- &lt;strong&gt;Challenging&lt;/strong&gt;:
Looking at some discussions on the net, I found that some people are complaining about getting rejected from Toptal, that&amp;rsquo;s it. It is not easy, it is not for everybody. That challenged me, and I am eager to take that challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing scrapy on El Capitan</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/installing-scrapy-on-el-capitan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 19:19:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/installing-scrapy-on-el-capitan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are trying to install Scrapy &lt;em&gt;globally&lt;/em&gt; via pip on El Capitan, you may go through some trouble related to &lt;a href=&#34;https://pypi.python.org/pypi/six&#34;&gt;six&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;OSError: [Errno 1] Operation not permitted: &#39;/var/folders/2r/m12cht2j3332gy6tlqd66xmw0000gn/T/pip-tAYZND-uninstall/System/Library/Frameworks/Python.framework/Versions/2.7/Extras/lib/python/six-1.4.1-py2.7.egg-info&#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more about this &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pypa/pip/issues/3165&#34;&gt;issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To fix this you can use virtualenv or simply install Python using brew:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
brew install python
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
sudo pip install scrapy
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker birthday 3</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/docker-birthday-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 20:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/docker-birthday-3/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hello It&amp;rsquo;s Docker&amp;rsquo;s year 3 :D, celebrations everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We @ Casablanca, had a Docker session by @SamuelTerburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to him, and to the guys behind the event.
&lt;!-- Docker project &amp; Docker Inc(Business --&gt;
&lt;!-- dockerCon16 --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;quick-notes:854321d5d5ad3284819c6b04d6c573a6&#34;&gt;Quick notes.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;docker-component:854321d5d5ad3284819c6b04d6c573a6&#34;&gt;Docker Component:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker Image should contains all dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker container =&amp;gt; secure, (Bundle the Docker image)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker Engine run the Docker container.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;docker-services:854321d5d5ad3284819c6b04d6c573a6&#34;&gt;Docker services:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker Swarm: Orchestrator to manage Docker container in a cluster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;docker-power:854321d5d5ad3284819c6b04d6c573a6&#34;&gt;Docker power:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Isolation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;!-- Docker data center VS Docker Cloud. --&gt;

&lt;!-- Docker alpine : Base docker image with basic system requirement. (5mb) --&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;docker-commands:854321d5d5ad3284819c6b04d6c573a6&#34;&gt;Docker commands:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker images&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker ps&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker run image_name&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker run alpine sh&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker run -d alpine sh  #run the container as a daemon&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker ps -a  #List docker images&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker log sharp_banach&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker stop image_name&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker run -R image_name&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;docker run --name static-site-2 -e AUTHOR=&amp;quot;Elhoucine&amp;quot; -d -p 8888:80 seqvence/static-site&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- http://192.168.99.100:5000/ --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/docker/docker-birthday-3/blob/master/tutorial.md#static-site&#34;&gt;TUTORIAL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>now</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 13:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, I am in Casablanca, here is a some of the things I am currently busy with, with no particular order:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am reading some books around Business, Startups, and Social psychology..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;last update: 25/03/2016&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now page inspired by &lt;a href=&#34;http://sivers.org/nowff&#34;&gt;Derek Sivers idea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 11:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[updated: 09/09/2016]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my personal blog AKA my virtual mind. Be careful while reading, some ideas may blow your mind. If that is okay with you, welcome to the club ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to comment or just to say hello, feel free to contact me via twitter or drop me an email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 11:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;hello:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Hello!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Elhoucine, JavaScript developer, swimmer, artist, passionate about music, video producing, and more..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/elhoucineaz&#34;&gt;@elhoucineaz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>