<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Elhoucine Azayou offcial website</title>
    <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Elhoucine Azayou offcial website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 11:49:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>is what we do matters ?</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/is-what-we-do-matters-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 11:49:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/is-what-we-do-matters-/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We often get busy doing what we do in our lives without thinking much about the meaning and importance or the impact of what we are doing, we keep running in all directions, work, family, friends, future, things to buy, dreams&amp;hellip; until we get exhausted, some of us keep the fight, while some take a time to connect and relax, but in all cases we all admit how hard and busy this life become.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-what-i-am-doing-matters:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Is what I am doing matters ?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a good question to answer, because after all what we do determines who we are and who we will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Is what I am doing worth telling to my children ?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A normal, safe life is boring to tell, only the weird, &lt;strong&gt;risky&lt;/strong&gt;, out of the box, &lt;strong&gt;hard&lt;/strong&gt;, unusual, &lt;strong&gt;challenging&lt;/strong&gt;, adventurous life is worth telling, and interesting, and capturing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;caring-about-the-world:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Caring about the world.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caring about the world is something meaningful, because &lt;strong&gt;we are not living alone&lt;/strong&gt;, and our lives depends on each other, and you are not only a citizen of your country, you are a citizen of the world in the first place.
If we cannot contribute to a better world, at least we can care about that, poverty, wars, children, climate change&amp;hellip; We can start caring about one of these (If we are not already), getting more information and spreading the message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;doing-art:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Doing ART!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;I want them to discover that they are artists;
everyone is an artist, a creator, and refiner of sensibility without knowing it.
--Yves Klein
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art is a form of freedom, because to do art is to listen to our inner voice, and imagination, it is about doing one&amp;rsquo;s original version. So rather that following instructions we create them. Do more art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-with-others:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Connecting with others.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;We are like islands in the sea, separate on the surface but connected in the deep.
― William James
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found that this is one of the most meaningful things on earth, connecting with other people, discovering new cultures. Travel is a way of doing that, and that&amp;rsquo;s why you will find travelers a happier and open minded people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-with-self:f0ce86dd8a375d181d9b42eb48ee774b&#34;&gt;Connecting with self.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;The most beautiful things can only be created by the most free minds!
― Mehmet Murat ildan
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freeing our mind, eliminate the garbage forced by our modern society, and making space for what matters, is the core to keep our life under control.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am committed in joining Toptal ?</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/why-i-am-committed-in-joining-toptal-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 16:50:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/why-i-am-committed-in-joining-toptal-/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you search on Google you will find similar posts with the same title as this post. Because writing a blogpost about it helps you speed up the process and get &amp;lsquo;Priority Access&amp;rsquo; to the Toptal platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, was that my motivation to write it ? Definitely Not!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the completing your profile section, I got asked if I want a &amp;lsquo;Priority Access&amp;rsquo; then I have to write a blog post on my website explaining
why I am committed in joining Toptal, I skipped it right away, because it simply didn&amp;rsquo;t motivate me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After skipping it, I asked my self, seriously, why I am admitted in joining the Toptal Web Developers Network anyway ?  And hell, yeah! the desire to answer this question, and write a blog post about it comes suddenly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is the answer to that why, summed in 3 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1- &lt;strong&gt;Freelancing&lt;/strong&gt;:
The obvious motivation is of course freelancing, after doing full-time job for a while, it didn&amp;rsquo;t work well for me, so I decided to work remotely, because simply I found it hard to stick in one place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2- &lt;strong&gt;Quality&lt;/strong&gt;:
Okay, looking at all the open-source platforms, where everybody try to sell them selves, and the need to deal with automatic examination and test which by the way easy to crack, it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the best option for me, so I had to look for better. Toptal selection is human made, and the process is serious. And that explains well the 3% promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3- &lt;strong&gt;Challenging&lt;/strong&gt;:
Looking at some discussions on the net, I found that some people are complaining about getting rejected from Toptal, that&amp;rsquo;s it. It is not easy, it is not for everybody. That challenged me, and I am eager to take that challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing scrapy on El Capitan</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/installing-scrapy-on-el-capitan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 19:19:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/installing-scrapy-on-el-capitan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are trying to install Scrapy &lt;em&gt;globally&lt;/em&gt; via pip on El Capitan, you may go through some trouble related to &lt;a href=&#34;https://pypi.python.org/pypi/six&#34;&gt;six&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;OSError: [Errno 1] Operation not permitted: &#39;/var/folders/2r/m12cht2j3332gy6tlqd66xmw0000gn/T/pip-tAYZND-uninstall/System/Library/Frameworks/Python.framework/Versions/2.7/Extras/lib/python/six-1.4.1-py2.7.egg-info&#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more about this &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pypa/pip/issues/3165&#34;&gt;issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To fix this you can use virtualenv or simply install Python using brew:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
brew install python
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
sudo pip install scrapy
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello</title>
      <link>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 11:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elhoucine.github.io/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a dummy blog post, Just in case you visit :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>